# **Dan Moulton**

dan.moulton@icloud.com linkedin.com/in/dan-moulton-59455b116 https://github.com/DanMoulton

# Full Stack Developer

Self-motivated full stack developer with almost a decade of experience developing software. Strong problem-solving, analytical and communication skills, with the ability to work effectively as part of a team and alongside clients. Passionate about technology and always eager to continue learning and growing as a professional. I enjoy participating in all stages of software development, from design to implementation.

## Skills and Technologies

- Angular
- React
- JavaScript
- HTML & CSS

- SQL and NoSQL
- Python
- .NET Framework
- Java

- Node.js
- Flasticsearch
- Cloud

REST API

## **Professional Experience**

11/2020 - PRESENT

### Asst. Director - Machine Learning

### Moody's Analytics

Moody's Analytics provides financial intelligence and analytical tools supporting clients' growth, efficiency and risk management objectives.

- Currently leading the UI and backend efforts on ML-driven projects, providing ways for engineers to store, enhance and extract data. Current projects are in the financial risks analytics space using Angular 15, Python and PostgreSQL.
- Built frontend and API applications from scratch for an internal document analysis tool that makes use of OCR and machine learning to extract data from PDF files, with the ability to tag and annotate documents which allows the machine learning models to learn from user input. Developed using Angular 11, NestJS, Python, MySQL, Elasticsearch and RabbitMQ.
- Participated in the development of MLFabric, a cloud-based platform that operationalizes machine learning models allowing users to deploy and reuse at scale. Developed using Angular 10, NestJS, Elasticsearch and RabbitMQ.

01/2019 - 11/2020

### Senior Technical Analyst

#### Kin + Carta

Kin and Carta is an innovation and digital transformation consulting firm with clients consisting of Fortune 500 companies.

 Played a key part in the development of an event registration system for a luxury automotive company. Frontend developed using Angular 7 and Bootstrap with a heavy focus on UX, backend developed using .NET Framework.

- Guided a team in the re-engineering of a leads-generating system, transforming it into a responsive web application and resulting in additional functionality and scalability. Developed using Angular 8 and Ionic Framework and Java Springboot.
- Participated in the modernization of a caller verification system for a leading financial services brand. Developed using ReactJS, Redux, GraphQL and Jest for testing.

08/2014 - 12/2018

### Full Stack Developer

#### Freelance

- Collaboration with graphic and web design teams in the creation of responsive user interfaces, using JavaScript, jQuery, HTML5, Less CSS, along with a variety of JavaScript libraries.
- Responsible for the building, maintenance and deployment of front-end and back-office applications.
- Development and implementation of services and APIs using .NET Framework.

## **Education**

01/2015 - 06/2021

### Computer Science Engineering

Universidad de Palermo (Buenos Aires)

## Languages

• English: First language

Spanish: Fluent